this song is called Sodom and Gomorrah
and the refrain of the song is don't
look back don't look back when the bells
of the future ring because sometimes you
just gotta let Sodom and Gomorrah burned
[Music]
front view is a promised land city
baby
your eyes to sting you can make
I know you will
[Music]
just keep your vision II in the front
raise your eyes to Cory
hi jr. is a pillar of salt
design story
[Music]
thing
girls future
[Music]
when the bells of the future
when they ring
[Music]
no one knew good or evil and Sodom and
but I know you
are not like that
Oh
you've heard the two
messengers we know the dangers mind
there's nothing for you in this town so
lay down your blood
I know
[Music]
when the bells of the future ring
the bells of the future
start
[Music]
my future
let every
but the future when they read
[Music]
in front of you is a promised land city
on the hill
and even though your eyes do sting you
can make it I know you will